BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 15) 6178/015
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Code no.591575: Teledyne Ryan Aeronautical Co. and United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America Local 506, 1960-1978 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Code no.590877: Sandia Corporation and Atomic Projects and Production Workers, Metal Trades Council, 1961-1982 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Code no.590898: St. Regis Paper Company and United Papermakers and Paperworkers Local 261, 1967-1972 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Code no.590936: Whitehead and Kales Company and United Steelworkers of America Local 2341, 1968-1980 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Code no.590961: Berkshire Hathaway Inc. and Textile Workers Union of America, 1959-1980 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Code no.590999: United Illuminating Company and Utility Workers Union of America Local 470-471, 1975-1980 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Code no.591013: Niagara Frontier Transit System, Inc. and Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, Div. 1342, 1960-1978 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Code no.591020: Sunstrand Heat Transfer, Inc. and International Union United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers Local 1218, 1974-1982 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Code no.591063: St. Regis Paper Company and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners Local 2581, 1963-1983 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Code no.591065: Maremont Corporation, New England Division and Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Local 406, 1975- 1981 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Code no.591102: Mechanical Contractors Association of Cincinnati and Pipefitters Local Union 392, 1976-1982 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Code no.591114: Arctic Enterprises, Inc. and International Woodworkers of America Local 4-348, 1974-1982 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Code no.591165: United States Playing Card Company and United Playing Card Workers Local 256, 1971-1980 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Code no.591168: SMACNA-Cleveland and Sheet Metal Workers Local 65, 1973-1982 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Code no.591182: Hobart Manufacturing Company and United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America Local 128, 1972-1980 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Code no.591205: Standard Brands, Inc. and International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers Locals 10, 42, 121, 159, 293, 317, 370, 1967-1976 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Code no.591211: Mason Contractors Association of Northwest Indiana, Inc. and Bricklayers and Allied Craftsmen Union Local 6, 1972- 1981 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Code no.591239: Allied Building Metal Industries and Shopmen's Local 455, 1959-1978 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Code no.591243: Cleveland Pneumatic Company and Aerol Aircraft Employees' Association, 1973-1982 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Code no.561229: Aro Corporation and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 1349, 1975-1981 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Code no.561325: Wood Conversion Company and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Local 158, 1963- 1965 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Code no.561360: Kimberly-Clark Corporation and United Paperworkers International Union Locals 692, 1693, 1595, 1971-1980 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Code no.561432: Detroit Edison Co. and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 17, 1974-1973 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Code no.561472: Borg-Warner Corporation, Stephens-Adamson and Sealmaster Divisions and United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America Local 1615, 1972-1978 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Code no.561511: Harbison-Walker Refractories and United Steelworkers of America Locals 76, 75, 66, 62, 95, 1974-1980 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Code no.561538: Square D Company and International Association of Machinists, Miami Lodge 2069, 1975-1981 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Code no.561560: United States Borax and Chemical Corporation and Mine Mineral and Processing Workers Local 30, 1974-1980 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Code no.561614: H.N.S. Management Company, Inc. and Amalgamated Transit Union Locals 281, 425, 443, 1975-1982 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Code no.561688: Brunswick Corporation and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 1764, 1976-1982 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Code no.561766: Glass Plate Industry NY and CO and Glaziers Local 1087, 1978-1981 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Code no.561864: La Crosse Rubber Mills Co. and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1968-1976 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Code no.561902: Todd Shipyards Corporation and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Local 469, 1972- 1978 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Code no.561924: United Parcel Service, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters Locals 229, 401, 429, 430, 764, 771, 773, 776, 1962- 1976 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Code no.561926: Metropolitan New York Nursing Home Association, Inc. and Registered Nurses Guild Local 144, 1972-1976 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Code no.561933: Ohio Brass Company and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 2158, 1974-1982 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Code no.570011: Pacific Telephone and Telegraph Company; Bell Telephone Company of Nevada and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 1269, 1971-1980 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Code no.570104: Westinghouse Electric Corporation and Plywood and Veneer Workers Local 3130, 1973-1982 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Code no.570200: Great Lakes Dredge Section and Seafarers International Union, Inland Boatmen's Union, 1972-1978 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Code no.570261: Dayton Press, Inc. and Dayton Printing and Graphic Communications Union Local 54, 1975-1983 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Code no.570284: New Bedford Gas and Edison Light Company and Brotherhood of Utility Workers of New England Locals, 333, 338, 339, 1975-1981 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Code no.570353: Duriron Company, Inc. and United Steelworkers of America Local 3320, 1969-1981 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Code no.570374: General Electric Company and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 1000, 1970- 1982 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Code no.570445: Overprint and Flock Industry in NY, NJ, PA, and MA and Textile Workers Union of America, 1972-1977 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Code no.570472: Bemis Company, Inc. and Textile Workers Union of America Local 281, 1972-1977 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Code no.570491: Portland General Electric Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1975-1981 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Code no.570499: Toms River Chemical Corporation and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers' International Union Local 8-562, 1974- 1980 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Code no.570528: Kansas City Power and Light Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 412, 1972-1982 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Code no.570548: Bucyrus-Erie Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1975-1981 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Code no.570552: Philadelphia Beer Distributors Association and International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 380, 1972-1979 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Code no.570663: Wisconsin Electric Power Company and International Union of Operating Engineers Local 317, 1975-1981 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Code no.570676: Greenlee Bros. and Co. and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Local 1553, 1973- 1978 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Code no.570680: Iowa Electric Light and Power and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 204, 1977-1981 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Code no.570757: Construction Industry Employers Association of South Central New York and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1975-1981 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Code no.570757: Building Employers' Trades Association, Inc. and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1975- 1981 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Code no.570758: Picker X-Ray Corporation and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 1377, 1970-1981 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Code no.570879: Potlatch Corporation and United Paperworkers International Union Locals 608, 712, 1977-1981 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Code no.570914: Fraser Paper, Limited and United Paperworkers International Union, 1976-1980 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Code no.570952: Kirby Lumber Corporation and International Woodworkers of America Local 5-114, 1973-1982 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Code no.571036: Appalachian Power Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 978, 1973-1979 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Code no.571053: Arnold Print Works, Inc. and United Textile Workers of America Local 523, 1975-1982 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Code no.571095: Pacific Power and Light Company and Pacific Power Council of the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1973- 1977 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Code no.571109: Cities Service Oil Company and Lake Charles Metal Trades Council, 1966-1979 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Code no.571166: Anderson-Tully Company and International Woodworkers of America Local 5-293, 1976-1981 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Code no.571230: FMC Corporation and United Steelworkers of America Local 12625, 1976-1982 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Code no.571234: Omaha Public Power District and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 763, 1973-1981 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Code no.571240: General Tire and Rubber Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America Local 22, 1973- 1979 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Code no.571244: Central California Meat Processors Association and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 506, 1973- 1976 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Code no.580212: Allied Employers, Inc. and Warehousemen's Union Locals 117, 599; Teamsters Union Locals 252, 378, 589, 1968- 1983 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Code no.590035: Cooper Airmotive and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, District 146, 1976-1982 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Code no.590073: Aluminum Company of America and Aluminum Trades Council, 1974-1983 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Code no.590152: Babcock and Wilcox Company and United Steelworkers of America Local 4396, 1970-1981 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Code no.590211: Bergen-Passaic Building Contractors Association and Laborers' International Union of North America Locals 34, 28, 409, 509, 346, 239, 321 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Code no.590219: Montgomery Ward and Co. and Warehouse, Retail, and Mail Order Employees Local 590, 1968-1980 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Code no.590225: Keyes Fibre Company and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Local 449, 1966- 1979 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Code no.590234: GTE Sylvania, Inc. and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America Local 1608, 1976-1982 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Code no.590245: Rochester Telephone Corporation and Rochester Telephone Workers Association, 1968-1982 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Code no.590362: Crown Zellerbach Corporation and Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Local 850, 1975-1981 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Code no.590424: Washington Metal Trades, Inc. and International Molders and Allied Workers Union Local 158, 1979-1982 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Code no.590436: Weyerhaeuser Company, Twin Harbors Region and Industrial Workers of America Local 3-2, 3-130, 1972-1983 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Code no.590437: KVP-Group and United Paperworkers International Union Local 323, 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Code no.590450: Hammermill Paper Company and United Paperworkers International Union Locals 1787, 1788, 1972-1979 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Code no.590477: Tootsie Roll Industries, Inc. and Bakery and Confectionery Workers' International Union of America Local 1, 1974- 1980 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Code no.590563: Essex International Inc., RBM Controls Division and International Union, Allied Industrial Workers of America Local 668, 1974- 1979 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Code no.590568: Woodwork Employers Association and Millmen's Local Union 1120, 1964-1975 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Code no.590613: Mead Corporation and Atlanta Printing Specialties and Paper Products Union Local 527, 1973-1977 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Code no.590615: General Telephone Company of Illinois and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Locals 51, 702, 1959- 1982 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Code no.590625: Colgate-Palmolive Company and International Chemical Workers Union Local 15, 1973-1982 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Code no.590636: Portland Cement Company and United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers, 1975-1978 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Code no.590637: Painting and Decorating Contractors of America and Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators, and Paperhangers of America Local 86, 1959-1982 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Code no.590638: Building Owners and Managers Association and Service Employee Union Local 6, 1971-1983 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Code no.590639: Sears, Roebuck and Co. and Retail Store Employees Union Local 876, 1977-1980 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Code no.590641: Chevron USA, Inc. and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union Local 1-547, 1977-1981 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Code no.590657: Roofing Contractors of St. Louis and United Union of Roofers, Waterproofers, and Allied Workers Local 2, 1977- 1983 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Code no.590688: Sheet Metal and Air Conditioning Contractors' National Association, Sacramento Valley and Sheet Metal Workers' International Association, 1975-1978 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Code no.590696: Kennecott Copper Corporation and United Steelworkers of America Local 485, 1961-1980 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Code no.590724: Celotex Corporation and United Paperworkers International Local 321, 1971-1981 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Code no.590725: Minneapolis and St. Paul Milk Dealers and Milk Drivers and Dairy Employees Union Local 471, 1973-1978 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Code no.590747: Westvaco, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Local 508, 1971-1979 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Code no.590763: New Orleans Public Service, Inc. and Co-Operative Street Railway Employees' Association of New Orleans, 1964- 1981 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Code no.590769: Union Oil Company of California and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union Locals 1-128, 1-326, 1959- 1981 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Code no.590788: Bars and Taverns in Santa Clara County, CA and Hotel, Restaurant and Hotel Service Employees Local 180, 1970- 1977 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Code no.590793: United States Pipe and Foundry Co. and District 50, United Mine Workers of America Local 12014, 1959-1980 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Code no.590795: Shenango Inc. and United Steelworkers of America, 1962-1980 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Code no.590822: Cone Mills Corporation and Textile Workers Union of America-, 1970-1972 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Code no.590844: Bakery Employers Council and Bakery Salesmen's Local Union 227, 1971-1978 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Code no.590876: Sandia Corporation and Office Employees International Union Local 251, 1961-1981 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Code no.6734: Hebrew Butchers Union, Local 234, 1976-1980 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Kosher Meat Markets in the Greater New York Area and the Hebrew Butcher Workers Union of Greater New York, Local 234 (1976), 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Agreement effective 01/01/1976 and expires on 12/31/1977. Covers 900 workers in New York, NY.
  - Item 2: Kosher Meat Markets in the Greater New York Area and the Hebrew Butcher Workers Union of Greater New York, Local 234 (1978), 1978-1980 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Agreement effective 01/01/1978 and expires on 12/31/1980. Covers 750 workers in New York, NY.
  - Item 3: Kosher Meat Markets in the Greater New York Area and the Hebrew Butcher Workers Union of Greater New York, Local 234 (1978), 1978-1980 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Code no.6749: Retail Clerks International Association, 1967-1978 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Kroger Company and the Retail Clerks Union, Local 368, AFL-CIO (1966), 1966-1970 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Agreement effective 08/14/1966 and expires on 02/28/1970. Covers 1000 workers in Dallas, TX.
  - Item 2: Kroger Company and the Retail Clerks Union, Local 368, AFL-CIO (1970), 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Agreement effective 03/01/1970 and expires on 03/03/1973. Covers 1150 workers in Dallas, TX.
  - Item 3: Kroger Company and the Retail Clerks Union, Local 368, AFL-CIO (1973), 1973-1975 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Agreement effective 03/04/1973 and expires on 03/02/1975. Covers 1300 workers in Dallas, TX.
  - Item 4: Kroger Company and the Retail Clerks Union, Local 368, AFL-CIO (1975), 1975-1978 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Agreement effective 03/02/1975 and expires on 03/04/1978. Covers 1250 workers in Dallas, TX.
  - Item 5: Kroger Company and the Retail Clerks Union, Local 368, AFL-CIO (1978), 1978-1981 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Agreement effective 03/05/1978 and expires on 03/07/1981. Covers 850 workers in Dallas, TX.
- Code no.6852: Fernandes Super Markets, Inc., 1975-1978 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Fernandes Super Markets, Incorporated and the Southeast Food Handlers Local Union, Local 4, AFL-CIO (1974), 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Agreement effective 07/01/1974 and expires on 07/10/1976. Covers 2500 workers in West Bridgewater, MA.
  - Item 2: Fernandes Super Markets, Incorporated and the Southeast Food Handlers Local Union, Local 4, AFL-CIO (1976), 1976-1979 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Agreement effective 07/12/1976 and expires on 07/09/1979. Covers 2150 workers in West Bridgewater, MA.
  - Item 3: Fernandes Super Markets, Incorporated and the Southeast Food Handlers Local Union, Local 4, AFL-CIO Amendment (1979) (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Agreement effective 03/06/1979 and expires on 07/09/1979. Covers 2150 workers in West Bridgewater, MA.
  - Item 4: Fernandes Super Markets, Incorporated and the Southeast Food Handlers Local Union, Local 4, AFL-CIO Amendment (1979) (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Fernandes Super Markets, Incorporated and the Southeast Food Handlers Local Union, Local 4, AFL-CIO Memorandum (1978), 1978-1980 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Agreement effective 09/12/1978 and expires on 10/31/1980. Covers 800 workers in West Bridgewater, MA.
  - Item 6: Fernandes Super Markets, Incorporated and the Southeast Food Handlers Local Union, Local 4, AFL-CIO (1980), 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Agreement effective 11/01/1980 and expires on 10/30/1982. Covers 800 workers in West Bridgewater, MA.
- Code no.6911: Retail Shoe Employees Union, 1969-1978 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Shoe Retailers League, Incorporated and Retail Shoe Employees Union, Local 1268, 287, AFL-CIO (1968), 1968-1971 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Agreement effective 09/01/1968 and expires on 08/31/1971. Covers 1200 workers in New York, NY; Nassau, NY; Suffolk, NY.
  - Item 2: Shoe Retailers League, Incorporated and Retail Shoe Employees Union, Local 1268, 287, AFL-CIO Memorandum (1971), 1971-1974 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Agreement effective 09/01/1971 and expires on 08/31/1974. Covers 1200 workers in New York, NY; Nassau, NY; Suffolk, NY.
  - Item 3: Shoe Retailers League, Incorporated and Retail Shoe Employees Union, Local 1268, 287, AFL-CIO Memorandum (1974), 1974-1977 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Agreement effective 09/02/1974 and expires on 08/31/1977. Covers 800 workers in New York, NY; Nassau, NY; Suffolk, NY.
  - Item 4: Shoe Retailers League, Incorporated and Retail Shoe Employees Union, Local 1268, 287, AFL-CIO (1977), 1977-1980 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Agreement effective 09/01/1977 and expires on 08/31/1980. Covers 800 workers in New York, NY; Nassau, NY; Suffolk, NY.
- Code no.591773: Auto Mechanics Local Union No. 362 of District no. 54, International Association of Machinists, 1976-1979 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Cleveland Automobile Association and Auto Mechanics Local Union, Local 1363, AFL-CIO (1979), 1979-1982 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Agreement effective 06/15/1979 and expires on 04/30/1982. Covers 819 workers in Cleveland, OH.
- Code no.591374: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO and the Grand Union Company, 1972- 1978 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Grand Union Company and Food Handlers Union, Local 371, AFL-CIO (1971), 1971-1973 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Agreement effective 06/14/1971 and expires on 06/10/1973. Covers 1300 workers in CT.
  - Item 2: Grand Union Company and Food Handlers Union, Local 371, AFL-CIO Memorandum (1973), 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Agreement effective 06/11/1973 and expires on 06/09/1974. Covers 1141 workers in CT.
  - Item 3: Grand Union Company and Food Handlers Union, Local 371, AFL-CIO (1974), 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Agreement effective 06/10/1974 and expires on 06/13/1976. Covers 900 workers in CT.
  - Item 4: Grand Union Company and Food Handlers Union, Local 371, AFL-CIO (1976), 1976-1979 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Agreement effective 06/14/1976 and expires on 05/12/1979. Covers 856 workers in CT.
  - Item 5: Grand Union Company and Food Handlers Union, Local 371, AFL-CIO (1979), 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Agreement effective 05/13/1979 and expires on 05/15/1982. Covers 750 workers in CT.
- Code no.591384: Retail Store Employees Union, Local no. 876; Retail Clerks International Assoc., AFL-CIO, 1976-1979 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Cunningham Drug Stores, Incorporated and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 876 (1974), 1974-1977 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Agreement effective 04/28/1974 and expires on 04/30/1977. Covers 950 workers in Wayne, MI; Macomb, MI; St. Clair, MI; Oakland, Mi; Livingston, MI; Washtenaw, MI; Lenawee, MI; Monroe, MI.
  - Item 2: Cunningham Drug Stores, Incorporated and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 876 (1977), 1977-1980 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Agreement effective 05/01/1977 and expires on 04/30/1980. Covers 900 workers in Wayne, MI; Macomb, MI; St. Clair, MI; Oakland, Mi; Livingston, MI; Washtenaw, MI; Lenawee, MI; Monroe, MI.
  - Item 3: Cunningham Drug Stores, Incorporated and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 876 (1980), 1980-1983 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Agreement effective 05/01/1980 and expires on 05/31/1983. Covers 856 workers in Wayne, MI; Macomb, MI; St. Clair, MI; Oakland, Mi; Livingston, MI; Washtenaw, MI; Lenawee, MI; Monroe, MI.
- Code no.590987: Retail Clerks International Assoc., 1971-1982 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Food Fair Stores, Incorporated and Retail Clerks Union, Local 1636, AFL- CIO (1972), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    Agreement effective 07/30/1972 and expires on 07/27/1974. Covers 750 workers in Tampa, Florida.
  - Item 2: Food Fair Stores, Incorporated and Retail Clerks Union, Local 1636, AFL- CIO (1975), 1975-1978 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    Agreement effective 07/27/1975 and expires on 07/29/1978. Covers 750 workers in Tampa, Florida.
- Code no.591095: Retail Clerks International Union, 1974-1980 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Incorporated and Retail Clerks Local Union, Local 1063, AFL-CIO (1975), 1975-1978 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    Agreement effective 05/11/1975 and expires on 05/06/1978. Covers 906 workers in Fulton, GA; DeKalb, GA; Clayton, GA; Cobb, GA.
  - Item 2: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Incorporated and Retail Clerks Local Union, Local 1063, AFL-CIO (1978), 1978-1981 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    Agreement effective 05/14/1978 and expires on 05/09/1981. Covers 819 workers in Fulton, GA; DeKalb, GA; Clayton, GA; Cobb, GA.
- Code no.590391: Retail Clerks International Association, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Incorporated and The Retail Stores Employees Union, Local 782, AFL-CIO (1976), 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    Agreement effective 05/09/1976 and expires on 05/06/1978. Covers 563 workers in Jackson, MO; Clay, MO; Platte, MO; Cass, MO; Johnson, KS; Wyandotte, KS.
  - Item 2: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Incorporated and The Retail Stores Employees Union, Local 782, AFL-CIO (1978), 1978-1981 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    Agreement effective 05/14/1978 and expires on 05/09/1981. Covers 800 workers in Jackson, MO; Clay, MO; Platte, MO; Cass, MO; Johnson, KS; Wyandotte, KS.